Guide to the Herbert H. Hyman papers,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Files
  - Office of War Information (OWI) Files, circa 1942-1946
    - Untitled, (2 Folders) (Box 16, Folder 3-4)
    - Surveys Division Memoranda #32, 42, 47, 61, 66, 71, 79, 82, 89, 97, 98, 1943, (2 Folders) (Box 16, Folder 5-6)
    - Memoranda and Reports, 1943-1944 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Memoranda and Reports, 1943-1944 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - DU-1 Reports A-L (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Untitled Binder (Appears to continue the previous DU-1 Reports) (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - NORC (National Opinion Research Center), 1947, 1964, 1983-1984 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Master Code Books for Surveys S-17, S-29, and T-17, 1942-1943, (3 Folders) (Box 17, Folder 5-7)
    - Office of War Information--Rationing, circa 1942-1944 (Box 17, Folder 8)